[{"body": [{"type": "au-fill-table", "title": "填一填", "stem": "完成表格", "table": {"title": ["", "一组", "二组", "一共"], "list": [{"one": "9个", "two": "7个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg"}, {"one": "5个", "two": "8个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/d1855a4119663766d6aaa7b21d24d83f.svg"}, {"one": "9个", "two": "8个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/480be6f2d92bce113cc00f6595b969c1.svg"}]}}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [16, 13, 17], "knowledges": ["20以内的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-18"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-fill-table", "title": "填一填", "stem": "完成表格", "table": {"title": ["", "一组", "二组", "一共"], "list": [{"one": "6个", "two": "9个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg"}, {"one": "7个", "two": "4个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/d1855a4119663766d6aaa7b21d24d83f.svg"}, {"one": "8个", "two": "3个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/480be6f2d92bce113cc00f6595b969c1.svg"}]}}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [15, 11, 11], "knowledges": ["20以内的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-18"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-fill-table", "title": "填一填", "stem": "完成表格", "table": {"title": ["", "一组", "二组", "一共"], "list": [{"one": "5个", "two": "9个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg"}, {"one": "5个", "two": "6个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/d1855a4119663766d6aaa7b21d24d83f.svg"}, {"one": "6个", "two": "8个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/480be6f2d92bce113cc00f6595b969c1.svg"}]}}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [14, 11, 14], "knowledges": ["20以内的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-18"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-fill-table", "title": "填一填", "stem": "完成表格", "table": {"title": ["", "一组", "二组", "一共"], "list": [{"one": "6个", "two": "9个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg"}, {"one": "6个", "two": "6个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/d1855a4119663766d6aaa7b21d24d83f.svg"}, {"one": "5个", "two": "6个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/480be6f2d92bce113cc00f6595b969c1.svg"}]}}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [15, 12, 11], "knowledges": ["20以内的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-18"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-fill-table", "title": "填一填", "stem": "完成表格", "table": {"title": ["", "一组", "二组", "一共"], "list": [{"one": "8个", "two": "7个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg"}, {"one": "7个", "two": "6个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/d1855a4119663766d6aaa7b21d24d83f.svg"}, {"one": "4个", "two": "7个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/480be6f2d92bce113cc00f6595b969c1.svg"}]}}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [15, 13, 11], "knowledges": ["20以内的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-18"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-fill-table", "title": "填一填", "stem": "完成表格", "table": {"title": ["", "一组", "二组", "一共"], "list": [{"one": "9个", "two": "6个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg"}, {"one": "9个", "two": "7个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/d1855a4119663766d6aaa7b21d24d83f.svg"}, {"one": "3个", "two": "9个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/480be6f2d92bce113cc00f6595b969c1.svg"}]}}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [15, 16, 12], "knowledges": ["20以内的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-18"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-fill-table", "title": "填一填", "stem": "完成表格", "table": {"title": ["", "一组", "二组", "一共"], "list": [{"one": "7个", "two": "5个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg"}, {"one": "7个", "two": "9个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/d1855a4119663766d6aaa7b21d24d83f.svg"}, {"one": "8个", "two": "4个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/480be6f2d92bce113cc00f6595b969c1.svg"}]}}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [12, 16, 12], "knowledges": ["20以内的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-18"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-fill-table", "title": "填一填", "stem": "完成表格", "table": {"title": ["", "一组", "二组", "一共"], "list": [{"one": "9个", "two": "4个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg"}, {"one": "6个", "two": "5个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/d1855a4119663766d6aaa7b21d24d83f.svg"}, {"one": "5个", "two": "8个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/480be6f2d92bce113cc00f6595b969c1.svg"}]}}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [13, 11, 13], "knowledges": ["20以内的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-18"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-fill-table", "title": "填一填", "stem": "完成表格", "table": {"title": ["", "一组", "二组", "一共"], "list": [{"one": "8个", "two": "3个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg"}, {"one": "7个", "two": "8个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/d1855a4119663766d6aaa7b21d24d83f.svg"}, {"one": "9个", "two": "7个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/480be6f2d92bce113cc00f6595b969c1.svg"}]}}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [11, 15, 16], "knowledges": ["20以内的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-18"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-fill-table", "title": "填一填", "stem": "完成表格", "table": {"title": ["", "一组", "二组", "一共"], "list": [{"one": "5个", "two": "8个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg"}, {"one": "8个", "two": "7个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/d1855a4119663766d6aaa7b21d24d83f.svg"}, {"one": "9个", "two": "9个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/480be6f2d92bce113cc00f6595b969c1.svg"}]}}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [13, 15, 18], "knowledges": ["20以内的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-18"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-fill-table", "title": "填一填", "stem": "完成表格", "table": {"title": ["", "一组", "二组", "一共"], "list": [{"one": "6个", "two": "8个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg"}, {"one": "4个", "two": "7个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/d1855a4119663766d6aaa7b21d24d83f.svg"}, {"one": "9个", "two": "8个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/480be6f2d92bce113cc00f6595b969c1.svg"}]}}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [14, 11, 17], "knowledges": ["20以内的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-18"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-fill-table", "title": "填一填", "stem": "完成表格", "table": {"title": ["", "一组", "二组", "一共"], "list": [{"one": "7个", "two": "6个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg"}, {"one": "9个", "two": "3个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/d1855a4119663766d6aaa7b21d24d83f.svg"}, {"one": "7个", "two": "4个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/480be6f2d92bce113cc00f6595b969c1.svg"}]}}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [13, 12, 11], "knowledges": ["20以内的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-18"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-fill-table", "title": "填一填", "stem": "完成表格", "table": {"title": ["", "一组", "二组", "一共"], "list": [{"one": "7个", "two": "5个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg"}, {"one": "4个", "two": "9个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/d1855a4119663766d6aaa7b21d24d83f.svg"}, {"one": "7个", "two": "9个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/480be6f2d92bce113cc00f6595b969c1.svg"}]}}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [12, 13, 16], "knowledges": ["20以内的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-18"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-fill-table", "title": "填一填", "stem": "完成表格", "table": {"title": ["", "一组", "二组", "一共"], "list": [{"one": "6个", "two": "7个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg"}, {"one": "8个", "two": "3个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/d1855a4119663766d6aaa7b21d24d83f.svg"}, {"one": "9个", "two": "7个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/480be6f2d92bce113cc00f6595b969c1.svg"}]}}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [13, 11, 16], "knowledges": ["20以内的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-18"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-fill-table", "title": "填一填", "stem": "完成表格", "table": {"title": ["", "一组", "二组", "一共"], "list": [{"one": "9个", "two": "6个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg"}, {"one": "8个", "two": "8个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/d1855a4119663766d6aaa7b21d24d83f.svg"}, {"one": "8个", "two": "9个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/480be6f2d92bce113cc00f6595b969c1.svg"}]}}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [15, 16, 17], "knowledges": ["20以内的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-18"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-fill-table", "title": "填一填", "stem": "完成表格", "table": {"title": ["", "一组", "二组", "一共"], "list": [{"one": "7个", "two": "7个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg"}, {"one": "7个", "two": "5个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/d1855a4119663766d6aaa7b21d24d83f.svg"}, {"one": "6个", "two": "7个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/480be6f2d92bce113cc00f6595b969c1.svg"}]}}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [14, 12, 13], "knowledges": ["20以内的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-18"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-fill-table", "title": "填一填", "stem": "完成表格", "table": {"title": ["", "一组", "二组", "一共"], "list": [{"one": "9个", "two": "3个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg"}, {"one": "7个", "two": "4个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/d1855a4119663766d6aaa7b21d24d83f.svg"}, {"one": "7个", "two": "7个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/480be6f2d92bce113cc00f6595b969c1.svg"}]}}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [12, 11, 14], "knowledges": ["20以内的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-18"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-fill-table", "title": "填一填", "stem": "完成表格", "table": {"title": ["", "一组", "二组", "一共"], "list": [{"one": "9个", "two": "9个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg"}, {"one": "8个", "two": "4个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/d1855a4119663766d6aaa7b21d24d83f.svg"}, {"one": "6个", "two": "9个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/480be6f2d92bce113cc00f6595b969c1.svg"}]}}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [18, 12, 15], "knowledges": ["20以内的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-18"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-fill-table", "title": "填一填", "stem": "完成表格", "table": {"title": ["", "一组", "二组", "一共"], "list": [{"one": "8个", "two": "4个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg"}, {"one": "5个", "two": "6个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/d1855a4119663766d6aaa7b21d24d83f.svg"}, {"one": "5个", "two": "9个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/480be6f2d92bce113cc00f6595b969c1.svg"}]}}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [12, 11, 14], "knowledges": ["20以内的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-18"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-fill-table", "title": "填一填", "stem": "完成表格", "table": {"title": ["", "一组", "二组", "一共"], "list": [{"one": "9个", "two": "6个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg"}, {"one": "2个", "two": "9个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/d1855a4119663766d6aaa7b21d24d83f.svg"}, {"one": "6个", "two": "8个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/480be6f2d92bce113cc00f6595b969c1.svg"}]}}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [15, 11, 14], "knowledges": ["20以内的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-18"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-fill-table", "title": "填一填", "stem": "完成表格", "table": {"title": ["", "一组", "二组", "一共"], "list": [{"one": "7个", "two": "7个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg"}, {"one": "6个", "two": "6个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/d1855a4119663766d6aaa7b21d24d83f.svg"}, {"one": "9个", "two": "4个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/480be6f2d92bce113cc00f6595b969c1.svg"}]}}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [14, 12, 13], "knowledges": ["20以内的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-18"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-fill-table", "title": "填一填", "stem": "完成表格", "table": {"title": ["", "一组", "二组", "一共"], "list": [{"one": "8个", "two": "6个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg"}, {"one": "3个", "two": "9个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/d1855a4119663766d6aaa7b21d24d83f.svg"}, {"one": "5个", "two": "9个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/480be6f2d92bce113cc00f6595b969c1.svg"}]}}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [14, 12, 14], "knowledges": ["20以内的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-18"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-fill-table", "title": "填一填", "stem": "完成表格", "table": {"title": ["", "一组", "二组", "一共"], "list": [{"one": "6个", "two": "7个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg"}, {"one": "6个", "two": "8个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/d1855a4119663766d6aaa7b21d24d83f.svg"}, {"one": "9个", "two": "3个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/480be6f2d92bce113cc00f6595b969c1.svg"}]}}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [13, 14, 12], "knowledges": ["20以内的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-18"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-fill-table", "title": "填一填", "stem": "完成表格", "table": {"title": ["", "一组", "二组", "一共"], "list": [{"one": "7个", "two": "4个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg"}, {"one": "7个", "two": "8个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/d1855a4119663766d6aaa7b21d24d83f.svg"}, {"one": "7个", "two": "9个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/480be6f2d92bce113cc00f6595b969c1.svg"}]}}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [11, 15, 16], "knowledges": ["20以内的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-18"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-fill-table", "title": "填一填", "stem": "完成表格", "table": {"title": ["", "一组", "二组", "一共"], "list": [{"one": "8个", "two": "6个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg"}, {"one": "6个", "two": "7个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/d1855a4119663766d6aaa7b21d24d83f.svg"}, {"one": "5个", "two": "7个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/480be6f2d92bce113cc00f6595b969c1.svg"}]}}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [14, 13, 12], "knowledges": ["20以内的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-18"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-fill-table", "title": "填一填", "stem": "完成表格", "table": {"title": ["", "一组", "二组", "一共"], "list": [{"one": "8个", "two": "9个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg"}, {"one": "4个", "two": "8个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/d1855a4119663766d6aaa7b21d24d83f.svg"}, {"one": "8个", "two": "5个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/480be6f2d92bce113cc00f6595b969c1.svg"}]}}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [17, 12, 13], "knowledges": ["20以内的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-18"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-fill-table", "title": "填一填", "stem": "完成表格", "table": {"title": ["", "一组", "二组", "一共"], "list": [{"one": "6个", "two": "5个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg"}, {"one": "7个", "two": "6个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/d1855a4119663766d6aaa7b21d24d83f.svg"}, {"one": "8个", "two": "7个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/480be6f2d92bce113cc00f6595b969c1.svg"}]}}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [11, 13, 15], "knowledges": ["20以内的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-18"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-fill-table", "title": "填一填", "stem": "完成表格", "table": {"title": ["", "一组", "二组", "一共"], "list": [{"one": "3个", "two": "9个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg"}, {"one": "9个", "two": "6个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/d1855a4119663766d6aaa7b21d24d83f.svg"}, {"one": "7个", "two": "6个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/480be6f2d92bce113cc00f6595b969c1.svg"}]}}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [12, 15, 13], "knowledges": ["20以内的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-18"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-fill-table", "title": "填一填", "stem": "完成表格", "table": {"title": ["", "一组", "二组", "一共"], "list": [{"one": "6个", "two": "8个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg"}, {"one": "7个", "two": "5个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/d1855a4119663766d6aaa7b21d24d83f.svg"}, {"one": "9个", "two": "4个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/480be6f2d92bce113cc00f6595b969c1.svg"}]}}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [14, 12, 13], "knowledges": ["20以内的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-18"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-fill-table", "title": "填一填", "stem": "完成表格", "table": {"title": ["", "一组", "二组", "一共"], "list": [{"one": "3个", "two": "9个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg"}, {"one": "3个", "two": "8个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/d1855a4119663766d6aaa7b21d24d83f.svg"}, {"one": "9个", "two": "4个", "imgUrl": "sphere_items/480be6f2d92bce113cc00f6595b969c1.svg"}]}}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [12, 11, 13], "knowledges": ["20以内的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-18"}]